{
    "id": "fe8edd7ab868480f8bd30f6592a78c4d",
    "title": "Perfect Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have not visited this town .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ....................................... with us for over five years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is working",
                "was working",
                "has been working"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They ............................................ each other for two years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have been knowing",
                "have known"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We have not been on friendly terms ...................................... nearly two years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What have you been doing .................................. 10 oâ€™clock this morning?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................ to my native place since last January.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am not",
                "have not been",
                "had not gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has not paid his monthly subscription ........................................ a year now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ....................................... in touch with each other for one year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "His son has been undergoing treatment ........................................ two months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... when have you been learning music?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}